Calix Huang

Freelance Developer

Experience in a number of programming languages, and being proficient in several of them, including Python, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Django, PHP, Ruby, and SQL. Excellent reputation for understanding and learning material quickly, communicating well, and working well with others.

Work History and Experience

2019-07 - Founder President

Current

HackSpace, Danville, California

Worked with non-profit organizations to develop a product for them at zero cost and high satisfaction, also while managing my team of high-school developers.

2019-02 -

Teen Leadership Council Member

Current

Trivalley CoderDojo, Dublin, CA

Supervised, presented, and mentored at Trivalley CoderDojo. Presented on technical topics such as web development, databases, and cybersecurity.

Mentored aspiring programmers in Python, Web Development, and Ruby.

2019-01 -

Media Volunteer

Current

The Rock Church, Danville, California

Voluntary technical support for weekly non-profit organization service. Contributed time to maintain media duties to summer camp with over 1,000 children.

2019-01 -Current

Web Developer Intern

Synergize Ventures, Danville, California
I design, develop, and maintain the Synergize Ventures
official website and add improvements to it.

Education

2018-09 -

High School Diploma

Personal Info

Address

100 Fairview St

Danville, California, 94506

Phone

(925) 332-6127

E-mail

calix.huang1@gmail.com

Technical and Soft Skills

Organizational Skills



Good communication



Fast learner



Current California Connections Academy - Ripon, CA

2018-09 - Online Certificiation: Software Development, Current Cybersecurity

Udemy - San Francisco, CA
Official Udemy certificates from topics including
Python, Full-Stack Web Development, Django, PHP,
Ruby, C++, Java, R, Swift, SQL, ethical hacking,
penetration testing, cybersecurity, browser automation,
Git/GitHub, various machine learning topics such as,
NLP, GANs, TSA, Deep Learning, Neural Networks, and
Computer Vision, and AWS technologies including S3,
SageMaker, RoboMaker, and EC2.

Accomplishments

2nd place at state-wide competition called CalPoly Cyber Innovation Challenge with team of high schoolers.

Top 20 fastest deepracers at AWS Summit in Santa Clara

Interests and Hobbies

Software Development

Competitive Tennis

Community Services

Competing in hackathons